Tudor Popescu

<u>LinkedIn • Portfolio • GitHub • tudor.m.p@outlook.com • +447465402934</u>

Summarv

Front-End Developer with 2 years of experience building and designing responsive web applications, specializing in React and Next.js. I have a sharp eye for intuitive design, and solid logic and maths skills. Driven by innovation and problem-solving, and creatively inspired by my passion for music.

Experience

Front-End Developer · WeJam, London

Jun 2022 - present

- Developing and implementing user-friendly, responsive, and mobile-first features for the WeJam React app using React and SASS.
- Overhauled the user interface of the React web app in line with the company branding, using SASS, CSS Animations, and Figma.
- Built several game modes, with their custom user journeys, including an accessible mode for children with special needs.
- Collaborated with the rest of the team on building in tandem cross-language features between the React/node and MaxMSP apps, which make up the WeJam software. Designed a custom Git workflow as MaxMSP isn't versionable.
- Lead the migration the WeJam project management system to Notion, to better track tasks, bugs and progress, which nearly doubled the team's productivity.
- Improved connectivity and fixed server request issues, preventing mid-session interruptions.
- Automated song scoring using Python and Lilypond, cutting in half the time to add a song to the experience.
- · Writing modular, reusable code following best practices.

Web and UX Designer · Freelance

Oct 2022 - present

- Delivered UX projects, such as for a sports booking app, to create a modern and consistent experience on mobile and web.
- Designed landing pages for clients such as Soundr and Wolfy's Bar, to promote new products and attract new customers.
- Designed logos to user specifications, blending the brand's identity and name into unique, memorable symbols.

Song Production Assistant • WeJam, London

2021 - 2022

- Creating song scores in Musescore, based on set of rules. Converting scores to json files using bespoke software.
- · Collaborating and tracking progress in Trello. Collaborating through Zoho Cliq and
- · Created UX project for improved game stats screen, which ended up being implemented in the app.

Projects

Kronos

Feb 2024 - present

Building a smart organiser app that goes one step further in understanding the user's

- Set up Next.js app, using TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, PostgreSQL and Prisma
- Created app code-base following best practices and OOP principles.
- Used Hexaflexa library for calendar, TipTap for markdown text editor, date-fns for date
- · Designed and implemented intuitive app interface.
- · Planned and implemented efficient organiser algorithm.
- · Set up local database in Docker. Deployed app to Vercel.

Skills

React Next.js Typescript Git SCSS TailwindCSS JavaScript Node.js Figma UX/UI Design Redux Playwright Python PostgreSQL Wordpress Prisma

Certifications

Front-End Engineer Professional Certification

Codecademy, 2024

Product Design Certification LoveCircular, 2022

Education

BMus Popular Music • 2.1 Goldsmiths, University of London • 2016 - 2019

Maths & Physics Baccalaureate • 95%

Andrei Saguna National College, Brasov, Romania • 2012 - 2016

Languages

English Bilingual

Romanian Native

French Intermediate

Passions

Tech and Al Innovation

Songwriting & Production

Sustainability

Design

Content Creation Alt Pop Culture

Habit Science

Popular Science